// for quiz 1: do an image (screenshot of modified periodic table) as question, or
// bother with the formatting of a square div with border with element symbol in middle?

const quiz1 = [
    {
        questionNumber: 1,
        question: "H",
        answers: ["Hafnium", "Hydrogen", "Helium", "Holmium"],
        correctAnswer: "Hydrogen",
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 2,
        question: "Na",
        answers: ["Sodium", "Neodymium", "Niobium", "Napthalene"],
        correctAnswer: "Sodium",
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 3,
        question: "Mn",
        answers: ["Manganese", "Magnesium", "Moscovium", "Molybdenum"],
        correctAnswer: "Manganese",
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 4,
        question: "Au",
        answers: ["Antimony", "Arsenic", "Astatine", "Gold"],
        correctAnswer: "Gold",
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 5,
        question: "N",
        answers: ["Neodymium", "Niobium", "Nitrogen", "Nihonium"],
        correctAnswer: "Nitrogen",
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 6,
        question: "C",
        answers: ["Carbon", "Zinc", "Cerium", "Calcium"],
        correctAnswer: "Carbon",
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 7,
        question: "Ag",
        answers: ["Actinium", "Silver", "Arsenic", "Platinum"],
        correctAnswer: "Silver",
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 8,
        question: "O",
        answers: ["Thorium", "Oganesson", "Oxygen", "Osmium"],
        correctAnswer: "Oxygen",
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 9,
        question: "Fe",
        answers: ["Fermium", "Francium", "Flerovium", "Iron"],
        correctAnswer: "Iron",
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 10,
        question: "Pb",
        answers: ["Lead", "Platinum", "Protactinium", "Tin"],
        correctAnswer: "Lead",
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 11,
        question: "B",
        answers: ["Bohrium", "Bismuth", "Ytterbium", "Boron"],
        correctAnswer: "Boron",
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 12,
        question: "Cm",
        answers: ["Cadmium", "Copper", "Curium", "Cesium"],
        correctAnswer: "Curium",
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 13,
        question: "Sn",
        answers: ["Antimony", "Samarium", "Tin", "Seaborgium"],
        correctAnswer: "Tin",
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 14,
        question: "K",
        answers: ["Calcium", "Potassium", "Krypton", "Copper"],
        correctAnswer: "Potassium",
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 15,
        question: "Ti",
        answers: ["Titanium", "Terbium", "Thallium", "Thulium"],
        correctAnswer: "Titanium",
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 16,
        question: "Sb",
        answers: ["Samarium", "Seaborgium", "Antimony", "Scandium"],
        correctAnswer: "Antimony",
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 17,
        question: "Pt",
        answers: ["Palladium", "Plutonium", "Platinum", "Protactinium"],
        correctAnswer: "Platinum",
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 18,
        question: "Ni",
        answers: ["Nobelium", "Nihonium", "Niobium", "Nickel"],
        correctAnswer: "Nickel",
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 19,
        question: "V",
        answers: ["Flerovium", "Vanadium", "Livermorium", "Mendelevium"],
        correctAnswer: "Vanadium",
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 20,
        question: "W",
        answers: ["Tungsten", "Zirconium", "Iridium", "Mercury"],
        correctAnswer: "Tungsten",
    },
];
